{
    "id": "eca99e3edb1d4dd3b285c2473a97b265",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ................................. his work with diligence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... his instructions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "follow",
                "follows"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This ......................................... interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... allow this to happen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "did not",
                "not did"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My trip to the USA ..................................... successful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He will be ........................................ very hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never ........................................ any demand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "raised",
                "raising"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ........................................ out of the room without looking at anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "walk",
                "will walk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He had been ............................................. at the top of his voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "crying",
                "cried"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Great deeds ........................................... never done by small men.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ......................................... never betray my country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "do",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "John ..................................... his leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has breaking",
                "has broken",
                "have broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}